So, my badass wants to get chikara no hyōri
Bōriden de kūridipa matahitotsudemo
I have reawakened for revenge
kōsoku-sareta rūru ni tatte
Hey, throw up your speech and
statue of liberty, body count
Oh, It's all because of God's apostles all
Yeah, we need someone to hit no one's zones all
I give back the life, you give me one
I placed you, yes, no, you are all
'Cause I'm back in this age, so let's go!
atarashī stāryu isshun
'Cause I'm back in this age, we can survive
mō tōku-sō ni smashed, no half was right
The day is silent
Trigger one two, on a bunch of bullshit
You'll never go
Throw my mic check, go, check one window
My mind gets free for a day
Let's get crazy, yeah, I'm a bubble, so watch out!
yudanai to kaosu
Don't let them go, super saiyajin
'Cause I'm back in this age, so let's go!
Our eyes hazy now, sunset no shū
'Cause I'm back in this age, we can survive
mō dōji tai nante getting rockers high
The day is silent
Go, time here, oh, oh, shut up, time here
You'll never go
I'm sick and tired, oh, yeah, I'm tired
Yeah